So my pants have been refunded by Denim Tears. So thank you, Denim Tears. But I do think this is a really good learning experience, right? Because everybody's kind of, not everybody, but the use of AI and the implementation of AI, because it feels like that was a canned message.
It really just undermines the experience of customers, because a lot of us really want to support a brand, and we want to feel supported in supporting that brand. Now, this is a two-way street, though, because customers, some of y'all, are so used to dealing with big box companies that you don't try to actually have an interaction.
You just immediately do a chargeback, et cetera, et cetera. I want to encourage everybody to know that moving forward, there's only going to really be two options, like big box and then mom and pop.
And mom and pop is not going to be able to handle your multiple emails and all the things. They're not going to be able to get you that thing within 24 hours.
You're going to have to shift in how you, you know, interact with these spaces.
I only came to social media because I had already sent an email through their portal, and then they responded, you know, please send us some photos or send us more information, which I did.
And then they responded with that. So that was the final conclusion. And, you know, once you tell me this is the final conclusion,
oh, now I'm just going to take it to the house. Take it to the house, take it to the house.
So, Denim Tears, I hope that you guys will take this as a catalyst for making some shifting and changes to your customer service, you know, methodology.
And I will also say this, someone came in the comments and was like, you, with your platform, you could have just contacted the creator of Denim Tears, etc.
Someone else said, oh, you should have somebody that is also the, that has a plug.
I should not need any of those things. I'm a consumer.
I didn't have a plug buy me the sweats.
I didn't get the sweats gratis from the creator of Denim Tears.
I bought them like everybody else online and I paid a grip.